{"data":[{"question":"The coins are ________ to be over a thousand years old.","a":"described","b":"said","c":"told","d":"mentioned","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the passive form of the reported speech","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Who will ________ Jean's cat while she is away?","a":"take care of","b":"take track of","c":"take advantage of","d":"get in touch with","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Take care of sbd\/sth: to look after someone or something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't like your ________ behavior. You are grown up but you are still ________.","a":"childish \/ childlike","b":"childlike \/ childish","c":"childish \/ a child","d":"childlike \/ a child","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Childish: behaving in a silly way that makes you seem much younger than you really are - used to show disapproval.\u00a0\n- Childlike: having qualities that are typical of a child, especially positive qualities such as innocence and eagerness.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you think I ________ to send my old lover a gift on her birthday? Peter asked.","a":"should","b":"had better","c":"ought","d":"must","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Ought to do sth: used to say that someone should do something because it is the best or most sensible thing to do [= should].","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"________ the rice so that it won't boil over.","a":"Set fire to","b":"Keep an eye on","c":"Pay attention to","d":"Put an end to","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Keep an eye on sth: to look after someone or something and make sure that they are safe.\u00a0\n- Pay attention to: when you carefully listen to, look at, or think about someone or something.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"John ________ every new girl he meets.","a":"takes care of","b":"takes track of","c":"falls in love with","d":"gets in touch with","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Fall in love with someone: to start to be in a new or different state.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you ________ the long distance telephone calls which you make in your office each month?","a":"pay attention to","b":"keep track of","c":"take advantage of","d":"get in touch with","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Keep track of somebody\/something: to pay attention to someone or something, so that you know where they are or what is.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"It is up to the police to ________ these robberies.","a":"keep an eye to","b":"pay attention to","c":"put an end to","d":"get in touch with","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Put a stop\/an end to something: to stop an activity that is harmful or unacceptable.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Sit here with us. We can move over and ________ you on this sofa.","a":"keep an eye to","b":"pay attention to","c":"make room for","d":"get in touch with","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Make room for: give space somewhere for a particular thing, person, or activity.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"No one knows who ________ the building.","a":"set fire to","b":"put an eye on","c":"pay attention to","d":"put an end to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Set fire to something\/set something on fire (= deliberately make something start burning).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"}]}